Yes, ma'am. Thank you. Sounds good.
>> Awesome. We'll start first with Sam
McDow. Sam,
>> hey, Gary. Congrats, man. Just a couple
things for you. The first one I wondered
is just, uh, what was it like to get the
call?
>> Oh, man. It was an unbelievable feeling.
Uh, you know, I felt like I was sitting
there waiting forever. So, uh, man, I
couldn't have been more excited to see
that area code pop up.
>> And also, you know, the first round pick
here in in Kansas City, I wanted to ask
you a little bit about Mansour Delane.
Tell me what give me a brief scouting
report of him both as a player and a
teammate.
>> Yeah, we got the best corner in the
league. That's all I know. So, y'all are
about to see.
>> We'll go next to Matt Derek. Matt,
>> there we go. Hey, Gary. Congratulations.
>> Thank you. Appreciate it.
>> Hey, how much contact and and did you
have with the Chiefs during the draft
process?
>> Uh, yeah, it it was it was pretty
minimal, you know. Um, you know, I think
it's kind of it's crazy how some of
these teams kind of uh do their work
and, you know, they like to hide who
they like and some like to show it. You
know, it's a it's a big chess match. So,
um, I'm just so excited, man. It's a
great opportunity for me to to learn and
develop and be under a great coach and
obviously behind one of the the best
quarterbacks of all time. So,
>> you know, and I know in the seventh
round things can get interesting and you
probably start getting calls from teams
that um want to sign you if you don't
get drafted. U, did anything like that
happen? Was were you kind of a
crossroads coming was just wondering
what was going to happen there at the
end of the seventh round and if you were
going to be an undrafted free agent?
>> Yeah, there was definitely um some
conversations that we were having uh
trying to figure out, you know, what was
going to go down. You know, as you said,
it gets kind of wild there at the end of
the seventh. So, um just just grateful,
you know, that I have this opportunity.
>> We'll go next to Jesse Newell. Jesse,
>> hey Garrett, congrats. I got a couple
for you. Uh number one, you mentioned
working with Andy Reid and Patrick
Mahomes. just what do you think that's
going to be like?
>> Oh, I I can only imagine, you know, I'm
I'm so excited um to be in a room with
those guys and uh Coach Reed and his
unbelievable offensive mind and and
obviously, you know, sitting behind
Patrick and and getting to learn from
him hopefully, you know, steal some
things from him and uh see see the game
through his eyes. Uh it's going to be an
unbelievable experience for me.
Something that, you know, I'm really
grateful for.
>> And you mentioned this is later than I
think anybody anticipated you'd go. Uh
can you just give me your reaction to to
that happening?
>> Yeah. Uh, I mean, you know, obviously it
was difficult for me sitting there, um,
you know, and and not understanding, uh,
why, I guess you could say. Um, you
know, obviously I have a belief in
myself and, you know, where I believe
that I should have been valued. And at
the end of the day, you know, I'm I'm
just grateful for this opportunity. You
know, I said throughout this entire
process, it's not when, it's where, and
I couldn't be more blessed to go to such
a great team, such a great organization.
>> We'll go to Nate Taylor next. Nate,
>> hello. Congratulations. Um,
>> appreciate it. My question for you,
Eric, is you you came back to LSU last
year, and I know there's plenty that you
wanted to prove, but what do you feel
like you learned about yourself last
year given you had to play through so
much injuries, um, as you're trying to
obviously develop and and sort of lift
your your draft stop?
>> Yeah, I went through a lot. Um, you
know, as you guys have learned about me,
I'm a big believer in my faith. Um, and
my faith is my foundation. That is who I
am. And so, um, having that foundation
in Christ, you know, that's how I got
through all the stuff that I went
through this year. Um, you know, that's
how I still am. Uh, you know, the same
guy I was before it and actually better
off because of it. So, um, it was a
tough tough deal to deal with throughout
this year. Uh, but, you know, as I said,
you know, I'm better off because of it.
>> We'll go to Herby Tobi next. Herby,
>> hey Garrett, congratulations. Welcome to
Kansas City.
>> I appreciate it.
>> Yeah, you're welcome. You come from a
quarterback family. Your father
obviously played quarterback in the NFL,
now offensive coordinator. What are the
emotions like for your family and
especially like with you and your father
knowing that you're following his
footsteps into the National Football
League?
>> Yeah. Uh it's awesome. You know, I spent
my whole life uh growing up just looking
up to him and you know, obviously he he
played for the Saints and and played for
a couple other teams uh in his career,
but you know, I always wanted to be like
him. Um and so, you know, I'm so
grateful to now have the chance to go
try and do that. So,
>> thanks Herby. It looks like that's all
the questions that we have for you. So,
we'll let you get back to celebrating.
Welcome to Kansas City.
>> I appreciate it. God bless.
>> Thank you. Talk to you soon.
>> Okay.